"Minister Kim's Dream Life"
Wait until it's done
You sprinkle some sand on it like this
(Former safety management team leader of ACT Asan Factory)
Wait until it clumps
Start sweeping again
(First day of work at ACT Asan Factory)
Just pour it out like this
- What?
- Very simple, right?
Dog food is here
As for water, just use water from the faucet.
I heard that tap water contains minerals and is better if you drink it.
- But...
- Feces stinks when piled together
So clean it up in time
Why should I...
After six o'clock in the evening, security will take over.
but during working hours
Don't forget this is our job
No
Why do the safety and health managers do this?
If you step on feces, you may slip and fall.
Slips and falls can be dangerous. This is a matter of safety.
If the excrement is not cleaned up, it will emit a peculiar smell.
Odor will attract mosquitoes, which is related to hygiene
Isn’t safety and health your responsibility?
OK I understand
That’s pretty much the handover work.
- What?
- Do you smoke?
You just showed me how to unclog the toilet
How to clean up dog poop
Is this the end?
follow me
This way
Listen carefully
I will only explain it once
Tuesday, May 20
(Safety Checklist)
Draw circles here, here and here
Occasionally draw a triangle or two
Then draw a circle
At the end of the month, take pictures of them all
Made into PDF
- PDF
- Send to headquarters
-Okay
- However
No one will read it at all
One more thing, 12 noon
Logistics trucks will depart from here
OK
You have to check whether the goods are packed
To avoid falling off on the road
It should be installed
But you still have to be like this
Pull the strap a few times to confirm.
If installed very securely
Just sign the form given by the logistics team employee.
In addition, we should do safety exercises collectively before going to work.
You have to stand in front of everyone and set an example
- Me?
- that's you
It’s very difficult for introverts to do this.
Me too before
That's probably all I have to explain.
Do you smoke or not?
But this is a factory with hundreds of people after all.
Isn't it necessary
A decent safety management system?
Do you have any qualifications in industrial safety?
- No
- Isn’t that the right thing to do?
we are all the same
If you don’t know how to do it, how can you manage it?
If you don't smoke, I'll go say goodbye to the dog.
Find a place to lie down until you get off work
You should be busy first
Oops, I almost forgot
give
If you have a team dinner, give me a call
(ACT Fried Chicken Grand Opening)
There is no other restaurant nearby that can handle an order for 120 people.
I will also give away a lot of free gifts. How about that?
If you are interested
You can even inquire about joining
Then I'm leaving. Good luck to you.
Sooner or later, reality will hit you hard.
Call me then
See you later
Hello, I opened a fried chicken restaurant
Lots of gifts for you
Come if you have time
Attention all staff
Thank you all for your hard work this morning
It’s lunch time from now till 1pm
Wish you all a happy meal
(Note: This door is broken and is strictly prohibited to be opened)
It’s time to eat!
They ran away in a swarm
Just to have an early meal?
It's so uncivilized. It's too barbaric.
- Sorry
- scared me
Are you the new leader of the security management team?
yes
follow me
By the way, about the truck
It seems pretty stable
Please sign here
Good
Let’s go!
Aren't you going to eat?
Why does everyone love running so much?
(ACT Asan Factory)
(People are iron, rice is steel, work safely without panic)
(Pick up meals on demand to avoid waste)
Oops, I forgot to say that
You must run to the canteen for lunch
Otherwise, I won’t even be able to drink the soup.
This team is lined up...
Isn't it?
Sorry
What's wrong?
The seaweed soup is gone
We don't have any anymore
hello aunt
Come in quickly
take it
thank you
- Thank you for your hard work
- You too, auntie
What are you doing? Didn’t you say it’s gone?
sorry
Really
Ouch
come on
Attention all staff. Are you satisfied with your lunch?
Afternoon class is about to start
Please return to your work station and be ready to work.
Episode 5: Rice Bowl
Where are the underwear? Do you want me to send some more?
(underwear)
No, that's enough
Where are the socks? Do you want more?
Socks are enough
I go home every weekend. Don't worry.
There are washing machines and dryers here
Do you think this is a prison?
Come on, can you use a washing machine?
Please, I'm the director of an IT company
What does this have to do with IT?
How is it?
Are the people there easy to get along with?
It doesn’t matter whether he gets along well or not
Anyway, I can't stay here for long.
Seriously
Are you sure you can still go back to the headquarters?
How many times do I have to say the same thing?
I'm just here to stay for a while.
I'll save some experience and go back to raise the tube.
Stop talking about these useless things. I'm dead.
Okay, I won’t say anything anymore
I'll make some more side dishes for you next week
Sorry, I'm really busy this week
You have to eat well, you know?
Got it
Soo Kyum...
(End of call Ha Zhen)
Why is she so nice to me?
How could you do this to me?
What did I do wrong?
keep working
No need to send it to me
No, it's okay
(Bai Zhengtai)
(Beyond telecommunications, connect you and me)
(I heard you were transferred to the factory
I bought you a practical bag)
(I will contact you often
Thank you for everything Soo Gyom)
Husband gives
These are eaten in the car
I also packed a few things you like to eat at night
The rest arrive at the dormitory
You have to put it in the refrigerator right away, remember?
Remember, why did you prepare so many things?
- Go back to sleep. It's okay.
- OK
There are too many things. Let me send you down.
Don't worry it's okay
No need to send it to me
Go in
- (Zero accident again today!
- ACT safety exercises)
Really terrible
How to do this?
two, three
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight
two, two, three, four
five, six, seven, eight
One, two, three, four
two, two, three, four
five, six, seven, eight
(Follow the process and strictly abide by the rules)
One, two, three, four
five, six, seven, eight
two, two, three, four
One, two, three, four
Safety slogan Get ready!
Safety slogan Start!
Safety helmet confirmed! Workwear confirmed!
Safety shoes confirmed!
- Safety first!
Instead of setting limits on yourself...
- It’s better to challenge firmly!
(Security Management Group)
(reception desk payment desk)
February 30th? No?
(Safety Checklist)
God, could they have been more perfunctory?
(2024 ACT Safety Checklist)
Really terrible
What on earth am I doing here?
Do you really want to consider joining Sang Cheol’s company?
It's really nerve-wracking
(Executive Director Bai Zhengtai)
It took two whole days and I finally got back.
(I will contact you often. Take care)
OK Good luck
Executive Bai, I respect your stupid decision.
But you said it yourself
We all have to be responsible for our own choices.
Then let's see how responsible you are
Because of losing Kim Nak-soo
And the shaky ACT sales team!
(ACT Building 1, ACT Building 2)
No, that's not... Oh my god, wait a minute.
Director, not section chief, it’s Kukkiwon
Their live broadcast was so stuck that it turned into a mess.
What should we do?
Minister Kim is the best at dealing with this kind of problem.
Do you want to call him?
What nonsense are you talking about? Give it to me
give
I am Director Du Zhenyu of the ACT sales team
Internet speed too slow?
Turn off the modem and restart it
Useless? Then...
Unplug the cord and plug it in again
Still useless?
- Impossible
- Then
Unplug the power cord and plug it in again
How about you pat the machine and pat it hard... Hello?
But one person left
A whole year of hard work was destroyed in three days!
You keep saying you are capable!
I just handed over a group to you!
If you can’t do it, stop bragging!
(Sales performance analysis)
Okay, you go out first
And you boy!
How dare you drag your slippers into the executive office!
Do you think I'm easy to bully?
- Right...
- Get out!
I'm so angry!
Luo Zhu, is that you?
Brother, it’s brother
I'm really sorry for you, it's just...
It seems you have to come back.
Once you leave, everything will be messed up.
Okay, you're just asking for humiliation.
Attention all staff
Thank you all for your hard work this morning
- Lunch time starts now until 1pm
-Sleep so comfortable
Wish you all a happy meal
I have to keep having this dream
It’s time to eat!
Really
Why did you come?
Hurry!
sign here
It’s too late to set off!
(Strawberry yogurt)
Each person can only take one box
What?
I said one person can only take one box
There's a lot left
Some colleagues finish their shifts late and eat late
Gotta leave some for them
I didn't get any soup yesterday
What?
I said I didn't get any soup yesterday, seaweed soup
You didn't get any soup yesterday
What does it have to do with picking up an extra box of yogurt today?
Makes sense
that
I'm from the sales team at the headquarters
So?
What?
Why are you telling me this?
Did the headquarters ask you to get two boxes of yogurt?
What is your attitude?
- young
- What's wrong?
Is this guy picking a fight with you?
"This guy"?
I don't know. He said he came from the headquarters.
So get an extra box of yogurt
- What?
- When did I say I came from headquarters?
So I have to get two boxes...
Which group are you in?
I am the leader of the security management team
I'll take you with me in the morning
Let’s do safety exercises together, remember?
Which group are you in at the headquarters?
- What's wrong?
- Morning...
Didn’t I just grab an extra box of yogurt?
As for embarrassing me so much?
Maybe he's constipated
Maybe people just get two boxes at the headquarters
Just get one more box. Just get one more box.
let him be
Let him take it
Oh my God, you guys don't know the rules!
I've been working at ACT for 25 years. A full 25 years!
Because I got an extra box of yogurt
Are you going to be humiliated like this? That's ridiculous
- Let him take it
- Give it to him
- Even at headquarters, he...
- It doesn't make sense
I don't want it anymore
Really, whoever likes to drink will drink
- I just...
- Originally it was one box per person
People at the headquarters might take two boxes.
Attention all staff. Are you satisfied with your lunch?
Afternoon class is about to start
Please return to your work station and be ready to work.
Because I got an extra box of yogurt
By a little girl of daughter generation
The unfortunate day of scolding is finally over
Songxi
Minister, I'm sorry.
Where did you put the locker key?
Just under the pot of orchids by the window
thank you
(Minister Kim Nak-soo)
- I'm not here...
- Senior
- Orchid
- ...Is it a mess?
- This basin?
- Are you there?
(Minister Kim Nak-soo)
Before he left, he told us something.
Give us a good meal
Why would he put it there?
Minister Do, what is that?
I see they are doing a buy one get one free promotion.
- Let's all have some.
- thank you
- What's your favorite flavor, Minister Dou?
You guys pick first and I can eat the rest.
Du Zhenyu!
(Minister Du Zhenyu)
- Du Zhenyu!
Goodbye
(Commitment to Safe Operations ACT)
(ACT Asan Factory)
Like the ebbing tide, employees leave work one by one
Only the night shift security guard and I...
And this little guy
Oh my god
Thank you for your hard work
What's wrong?
Not that after work...
We don't have any anymore
- Thank you for your hard work
- You too, auntie
What are you doing? Didn’t you say it’s gone?
sorry
OK Good luck
Did the headquarters ask you to get two boxes of yogurt?
Why do you think you stopped him from getting the yogurt?
This is wrong, this is impossible
Minister Kim Nak-soo, the great ordinary person of Korea
There is no way it could end like this!
Hurry up!
Run faster!
(One month later)
You are too full
But the funny thing is...
Mero, why are you eating in small bites?
- Gotta eat like this
- doesn't matter
- Look at you gobbling it up
- I'm starving
That me...
- Think about it
- Aren't you going to eat?
I'll give it to me
The meeting will end here
I have something to report in the future
Just tell me in person. No need to write a report.
Instead of wasting time on font formatting
Why don't you come to me directly?
You can say it anywhere
- Even a tea room is fine
- OK
- Yes I understand
- Yes
But forget about the bathroom. That would be a bit embarrassing.
It's obviously boring, but it's also inexplicably funny
- super funny joke
- Be quiet
I never think my ideas are necessarily right
So regarding the operations of our integrated sales team
If you have any suggestions
or a place where you wish to discuss
Please feel free to bring it up
I will listen with an open mind. Thank you. The meeting is dismissed.
Section Chief Song
Let's get together sometime and have a meal together.
- What do you think?
- Very good
Very good
Senior, I look forward to working with you.
OK
Please give me more advice in the future
please
Section Chief, I would like to call today
"ACT Spring"
Are you saying that Minister Kim is Chun Doo-kwang?
"If you succeed, raise the pipe
If you fail, you will be moved to the left!"
Stop it. Aren't you afraid of retribution?
OK
Section Chief, you must be delighted too, right?
Isn't it?
We used to waste three days a week
Create presentations that only we can see
It's good to be able to save this time now
See? He's just like us
He doesn't want Minister Kim to come back either
But I feel quite bad
It can happen to any of us
I'm also worried about whether he can adapt to it.
Then I will go on a business trip to Asan next month.
Just let Section Chief Song go.
- You can drop in and see the minister.
- good idea
Ready? Rock, paper, scissors
No scissors allowed, rock paper scissors
I told you not to bring out scissors
Bon voyage
(Koto Real Estate Broker Examination Academy)
Oh my god
What are you sighing for?
My family's situation does not allow me to take the exam for the third time
What's the use of being nervous now? Isn't it enough just to pass the exam?
I can no longer touch my husband’s retirement pay
I really can't fail this time
I must pass the exam this time too
No matter what, you must pass the exam
How many pages are you talking about?
- Page 114
- This...
I know every word, but I can’t understand even the words.
Then memorize it by rote
Very good
OK
Abominable
So hot
What are you doing?
Oh my god
So hot
Their fried chicken is still delicious even if it's cold.
Team Leader Kim
hello
Did you eat it?
Not yet
(old-fashioned fried chicken)
Then eat quickly
Let Brother Dazai bring a pizza on the way here.
Why did she come?
I'm starving
There should be no traffic jam here
Wife?
Why did you come back so late?
Suqian, can't you go home early?
I'm back!
Let's get started
It's my turn again
- What are you doing?
- drink
work
(To be busted: meaningless company parties)
- OK
- Done
I'll go report to the representative.
Now?
We are having a party
No need to draw a clear line between work and play
This is exactly what the representative said
OK
Hurry up
Wait
You need to drink this
Come again
- Why?
- come again
hey
Hurry up!
It's already nine o'clock. Why aren't they back yet?
Where have everyone gone?
She didn't even answer the phone
Hello husband?
- Hello
- What's going on?
What are you doing?
(Limited time special offer for intensive classes)
That me...
I...
I'm watching a movie with Ha Young. What's going on?
What time does the show end?
It will probably start around 11 o'clock
What's the matter?
It's okay. Just take a good look.
Okay, then you take a taxi back
It's a taxi home
OK
She could have watched it with me
(Dad)
What's the matter?
It's okay
The number you dialed...
Is there still a meeting at this point?
Who are you lying to?
Really
Those are daddy's shoes
That's right
What to do?
Oh my God, you scare me to death!
When did you come back?
I bought fried chicken. Let’s eat together.
I'm not very hungry
I'm not hungry either, Dad
Really? It seems a little late
Then I’ll take it back to Asan to eat
That's not okay. Let's eat together.
- It's okay
- Looks like it smells good
- Don't force it
- Have a seat
It's been a long time since our family had a midnight snack. Come on
Let's get started
I started eating
It's all cold
Their fried chicken is actually quite delicious.
Now that you're back, I'll bring some side dishes with you tomorrow.
No, the food in the cafeteria is pretty good.
you have to eat healthy
It's okay. The food in the factory is good.
Soo Kyum
What have you been doing lately? Coming back so late
Um, yes
What did I do today?
What did you say?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight
two, two, three, four
five, six, seven, eight
One, two, three, four
- Logistics team!
- Five, six, seven...
Where are you going?
six, seven, eight, two, two, three, four
- Unload it
- five, six, seven
- The forklift is here!
- eight, one
two, three, four
OK, put down the lock!
One, two, three, four, five...
Don't you wear earplugs?
- What?
- Aren't you wearing this?
To prevent hearing loss, be sure to wear earplugs
- thank you
- You're welcome
Let's all have some ice cream to cool down.
Come all over
It's snack time
It's so hot inside
thank you
Thank you!
- Thank you!
Come and get it
- thank you
- Oh my god, it's so sweet.
Who else wants it?
give
The outer diameter is out of tolerance. Just adjust it a little smaller.
- Then...
- Not adjusting the temperature of the extruder
Need to make fine adjustments to the mold
- Got it
- OK
It doesn't matter. I'll finish here.
We're also going to check the pump lines.
Okay, you go
It's time to get off work, won't you go, Monitor Li?
Sorry, what did you say?
Do you have any plans for the evening?
Do you want to work overtime?
I would rather
But recently the company doesn’t allow overtime and extra shifts
Why do you ask?
If you have time, how about having dinner together?
Or just have a drink. It's up to you.
It feels like we haven't had a good conversation
not once
Just the two of us?
Yes No?
my treat
What do you like to eat, Monitor Li?
I found a store in front of me
They sell crock pot roasted pork belly.
If you want to eat pork belly, just eat it here.
Baking pans and tongs are all ready-made
Here?
- I mean...
- Joo Young!
Can you come over here?
OK!
Arrive at the safety management team office at seven o'clock
I will prepare everything
OK then
- See you later
- Goodbye
What's wrong with eating out?
- I almost forgot
- What?
We have everything but no meat
Oh meat
It’s impossible to eat barbecue without meat.
Give me the pork neck
- See you later
- Goodbye
Here I come!
The biggest problem for our company is...
(excessive phenomenon)
...endless meetings
But it rarely translates into constructive results
Most of them are only in the conceptual stage.
- It's you, right?
- No
please
- Pay attention
- And
Too frequent party culture
The harm is greater than...
- Hey JJ
-JJ?
- What's wrong?
- Hey it's JJ
-JJ?
- Are you in Korea?
- He should be in Korea
- What?
It reduces work efficiency
- It also kills the company's potential...
- Soo Gyom, sorry, wait a minute.
Who's free tonight?
It's DJ Claude's listening party
He said he could help us get a good location
Me!
- Me!
- It sounds exciting
yes five people
Where is Soo Gyeom?
our chief disruption officer
I've been having a headache lately hearing about parties, right?
- What does it mean?
- Not interesting
Don’t you hate parties?
That's why you do this, isn't it?
- It's not what you said
- sorry
Okay, see you then
It must be fun
I'm really sorry. Can you continue?
our chief disruption officer
What are you doing?
What?
I can't do it anymore!
(Kim Soo-gyeom)
What happened to him?
- Are you going to resign?
- Yes!
It's not a good idea to resign this way, right?
You are the biggest problem
- and all of you
- Me?
What on earth are you doing here?
What kind of company is this? Doesn’t it work?
What exactly do you mean by "work"? Make it clear
don't order me
You never made things clear
Because I am the one who holds the direction
Save yourself the bullshit, asshole.
You can't fool me anymore with your nonsense.
I will continue to go my way
Like a true Korean
Keep living like this
Don't look down on my way of life, you bastards!
Because it's great
- Okay, that's great...
- shut up
obey
Is it baked?
Can it be eaten?
Then say it
What?
Don't you have something to say?
That...
What’s the secret to your leadership?
What?
I have led the team at the headquarters for several years.
But people down there always have their own ideas.
Everyone only has their own interests in their eyes.
You know what I mean?
I can't tell
I find that people here are very convinced of you
Really?
Tell me what's your secret?
Are you being particularly nice to them first?
When they cross the line, then give them a harsh punishment?
- What?
- I mean
I want to know if you
Have its own management philosophy
What if I had?
So can I ask you for some tips?
The trick?
first
Once or twice a month
I will organize a reading club for employees
Reading club...
Like Carnegie's "Human Weakness"?
yes
every quarter
We will also rehearse a play
- Drama?
- There is also group meditation
Got it, group meditation
Are you talking nonsense?
Do you think this is funny?
Very funny
Really
Who has time for those tricks?
We were all exhausted to death
I just want to get drunk and fall asleep
Also Carnegie...
Seniors are humbly asking for advice
when i asked
Why don't you give some serious answers?
- What are you going to use it for after learning it?
- What do you think?
It will come in handy when I get back to the headquarters and go up to the supervisory level.
Will you return to headquarters?
Of course
What? You think I can’t go back?
yes
Can't you see clearly where you are?
According to the Major Disaster Punishment Act
Companies with more than 100 employees
A person in charge of safety management must be appointed
But it doesn’t matter who it is
As long as someone fills the hole, it will be fine
This is exactly
Those high-paid and incompetent people in ACT
The workplace terminal for white-collar workers
This is your place, Team Leader Kim.
It's hard to say that. I'm sorry.
But every time the headquarters sends a layman
We are the ones who suffer
See this?
The injury I sustained while loading and unloading cargo last year
Then what should I do? You can tell me
I have been working for 25 years like this
It’s the first time I’ve been so busy from morning to night
Do you know?
I don't want to be idle I want to work
You should tell me what I should do. I really don’t understand.
Except sweeping dog poop
In addition to doing meaningless safety exercises
I'm talking about real work.
There is no such thing
You don't have to learn anything or help us.
Just stay quiet
Then leave when you want to leave
That's enough
Isn't it?
There is something
It's summer now
Be sure to change the puppy’s water frequently
After all it is summer
(The monthly salary will be cut off and the monthly rent will not be)
(ACT Fried Chicken Grand Opening)
Just stay quiet
Then leave when you want to leave
That's enough
I forgot
This is leftist migration, this is exile
It's a punishment that wants to force me to resign voluntarily.
It's time to make a decision
What is this?
(March 14, 2007
I seem to be in big trouble)
(March 23, 2007 doing nothing)
(March 18, 2007 Missing a child)
It turns out to be an exile diary.
I'm back
What are you doing, Mom?
learn
Aren't you meditating?
is studying
ok
It is against the law to have false qualifications for three times
Sales knowledge exceeds the erroneous prohibition of direct bidding group
Unlimited broken...
(Real Estate Certificate Examination Preparation Guide)
(Closed)
Unlimited punishment, suspended suspension, suspension, withdrawal and penalty law
(Continued from diary on June 17, 2008)
(Why should I sweep up dog poop?)
It really has a long history, good guy
(...a boss who rises to the top through connections)
(Headquarters called again on November 17th)
(I feel like I have value again)
My nickname is "Amateur Otani"
Ohtani in amateur baseball circles
Call me next time
I don't know much about baseball. I only play football.
I also play football
Call me next time
I am still Haaland in amateur football circles
I've seen you play football. Where's Haaland?
I took training classes and made a lot of progress
Your motor nerves must be very developed
Let’s play football together next time
- Really?
- Really
that's great
(Minister Kim Nak-soo)
- Sorry, let me take a call.
- It's okay
Hello, Minister
Hello it's me
How are you doing?
Stop doing this
You've been flattering Du Zhenyu all morning, right?
How is it possible?
A gentleman has nothing to do with two masters, Minister
Then why haven't you even called me for a month?
I'm busy planning the wedding
You know I have to start a family too
Okay. I have something to ask you for help.
No problem. Just ask. Please speak.
A few years ago...
yes
(17th Real Estate Agent Examination)
- Examination room No. 1 is at...
- over there
(Real Estate Agent Examination Center can be found here)
The admission time is about to close. Please enter the examination room as soon as possible.
Examination room No. 1 is on the left. Examination room No. 2 is on the right.
Start now
Real estate agent exam first session
Candidates please fill in the answer sheet
(The first session lasts 100 minutes)
Exam starts
Have you checked it out?
Monitor, look
Attention all staff
Thank you all for your hard work this morning
It’s lunch time from now till 1pm
Wish you all a happy meal
It’s time to eat!
Very good!
- Give it to me!
- Sign here
Hurry up!
Have you checked it out?
Found it, Minister
I asked the human resources staff at the same time.
As you said, there is indeed such a person
Transferred back to the headquarters from the factory
He is Special Agent Shen Kangxun
Same situation as you, Minister, in 2008
He was transferred to the ACT Technical Security Management Group
Later, when I returned to the headquarters, I was promoted to the position of Special Agent
I finally got his contact information
This will be sent to you
But how did you know this person?
(Instead of setting limits on yourself, challenge yourself resolutely)
What?
What's going on?
Go around. You can't go here.
(December 16, 2008)
After suffering in this hell for 182 days
I'm finally going back to headquarters
don't give up hope
now it's your turn
I don’t run to fight for food
It’s not just to win over this little girl.
I run to prove that this punishment is wrong
It’s for me, Kim Nak-soo
As Minister Kim of ACT Group
Return in an upright manner
This is the meaning of my running
(canteen)
Enjoy your meal
And since you like that dog so much
It's up to you to wash the water bowl.
I must go back at any cost
"Minister Kim's Dream Life"
You guy... come back!
Transfer Kim Nak-soo back to the headquarters, senior
People I can turn to
The only one left is you, senior
- Chengjiu!
- Minister!
But you still have to take good care of him.
I might have to work under him someday.
The bad guy Kim Nak-soo would like to say hello to you.
You are on the sales team anyway
There's no one else to rely on
At this time
You need to show more loyalty
Otherwise, how could there be a turnaround?
Human Resources Group
The biggest battlefield this year is the Asan factory
Senior
We need your help
Ha Jin, I’m sorry.
I got into big trouble
Subtitle translation: Jia Xue